let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the highest grossing movie of all time?",
    answer: "Avatar",
    options: [
      "Avengers:Endgame",
      "Titanic",
      "Avatar",
      "Gone With The Wind"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who actually drew the sketch of Rose in Titanic?",
    answer: "James Cameron",
    options: [
      "Leonardo DiCaprio",
      "Billy Zane",
      "James Cameron",
      "Kathy Bates"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who was the first black person to win an Oscar?",
    answer: "Hattie McDaniel",
    options: [
      "Hattie McDaniel",
      "Sidney Poitier",
      "Dorothy Dandridge",
      "James Earl Jones"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "If you watch the Marvel movies in chronological order, which movie would you watch first?",
    answer: "Captain America: The First Avenger ",
    options: [
      "Iron Man",
      "Captain America: The First Avenger ",
      "Doctor Strange",
      "Captain Marvel"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which Nolan film has the highest average score on rotten tomatoes?",
    answer: "Dunkirk",
    options: [
      "Inception",
      "Prestige",
      "Interstellar",
      "Dunkirk"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who was the first Indian to win an Oscar?",
    answer: "Bhanu Athaiya",
    options: [
      "Anil Kapoor",
      "AR Rahman",
      "Bhanu Athaiya",
      "Satyajit Ray"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "For what movie Leonardo DiCaprio has won his only Oscar?",
    answer: "The Revenant",
    options: [
      "The Revenant",
      "The Wolf of Wall Street",
      "Titanic",
      "The Departed"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What was the first sound movie of India?",
    answer: "Alam Ara",
    options: [
      "Alam Ara",
      "Raja Harishchandra",
      "Sholay",
      "Mughal-E-Azam"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which actor has not played the Joker?",
    answer: "Sean Penn",
    options: [
      "Jack Nicholson",
      "Sean Penn",
      "Jared Leto",
      "Mark Hamill"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the name of the robot in Interstellar?",
    answer: "TARS",
    options: [
      "PANS",
      "OSHA",
      "MARS",
      "TARS"
    ]
  }
    ];